indianeagle.com 2016-11-20

# Privacy Policy | Indian Eagle

We at IndianEagle abide by our Privacy Policy to serve your travel needs, provide you with the right information, ensure your personal information security and assure you of the best service quality. We strive to improve our service standards and enrich your user experience in compliance with our Privacy Policy. You are requested to go through the "Privacy Policy" terms, and know about how we collect, use and protect your personal information. Your agreement to the Privacy Policy will enable you to get the best of our services.

#### **We share your information with the following groups**

#### **Suppliers**

Suppliers refer to airlines that we are associated with. We feature flight deals of the suppliers on www.IndianEagle.com. We share customers' personal information with relevant suppliers. They are given access to your personal details so that they can satisfactorily meet your travel needs. The relevant airline that we book your flight with may contact you and verify the details shared by you. You must check the privacy policy of the airline whose flight service you avail through IndianEagle.

#### **Third-party vendors**

Our associates include credit card verification agents, fraudulence investigators, customer service executives and business analysts in the group of third-party vendors. We provide the third party vendors with access to your personal details so that your request for flight booking is efficiently processed. We authorize only those whose services are relevant to your request for flight reservation, to access your details and contact you.

#### **Business partners**

Business partners in our network are the service providers whom we have associated with to improve and extend our services. If the service of any of them is required to serve your travel needs, we give them access to your information. We request you to check our business partners' privacy policies which are out of our control.

#### **Corporate affiliates**

Our corporate affiliates are various services providers in travel and non-travel niches. We market and promote each other. We may share your details with them in order to facilitate your access to their services. They apply fool-proof security measures to protect your vital details shared with them.   
The above-mentioned groups of our associates are bound to abide by their privacy policies in order to prevent your identity theft and protect your personal information. 

#### **What personal details we collect and how we use them**

Browsing our website IndianEagle.com does not require you to share or provide any personal detail. We require you to share with us some personal information when you sign up for our newsletter, open "My Eagle" account on our website IndianEagle.com, or book your trip with us.   
Your first name, last name, email ID, mailing address and contact number (telephone or fax) are the basic details that we request you to share with us. You are asked to provide the credit card number and credit card expiration date only when you book your trip with us. With the help of your information, we identify you as a genuine user. 

#### **Booking and purchasing**

Sharing your personal details (mentioned above) is mandatory in order to book a flight and make payment for the same. We may need your 'frequent traveler' number to process your 'flight booking' request and notify you of the earned points. If you want to book a flight for the other person, you need to provide his / her personal details.

#### **Member enrollment**

For member enrollment, you need to create a "My Eagle" account using unique username and password on the website. You are required to share with us the above-mentioned personal details while creating an account for member enrollment. We use the shared details for user identification, identity checking, registration confirmation, booking confirmation, payment transaction and information improvement. 

#### **Member profile completion**

Once your "My Eagle" account is created, you need to fill up the member profile with the above-mentioned personal details for successful enrollment. Having a complete member profile you are able to avail our services quickly.

#### **Online surveys**

We, at times, conduct online surveys among our existing customers, registered members and potential users to know their travel needs as well as preferences. Participating in the surveys is optional. Your valuable opinions help us improve our customer service, flight booking service, website and its content. Your preferences in regard to destinations help us notify you of the available cheap flight deals for those destinations.

#### **Rewards program**

IndianEagle has a unique Rewards program for the registered users. With the program, you are entitled to receive points for online member enrollment and flight booking. The earned Rewards points are redeemable for discount on subsequent flight bookings. In order to enroll for the program, you need to share your personal information and contact details with us. Using your contact details, we notify you about the earned points and the user account status.

#### **Cookies**

"Cookies" refers to small pieces of information that are saved on your computer when you browse the Internet. The details of your computer are traced only by the servers that use cookies. However, cookies are no spyware or malicious application to collect your personal details. It is a common facet of Internet. Our service uses cookies for the purposes given below:

  * We use cookies to improve our service quality and enrich your user experience. Our server cookies do not require you to enter the username at the time of logging in to your "My Eagle Account" on IndianEagle.com. You need to use the password only. 
  * We use cookies to ensure and enhance your "My Eagle Account" security. Our server cookies collect your member ID when you sign up on IndianEagle.com. 
  * We use cookies to identify you as a frequent visitor on our Website. It also helps us know your travel preferences from the data that you enter on our website, and serve your needs accordingly 
  * We use cookies to evaluate the interactivity of our Website and its communication efficiency. 

Almost all Internet browsers let server cookies collect user computer details. You can restrict the browser that you use to surf Internet and visit websites from accepting cookies, through customization of the setting or anti-cookies application installation. 

You have the right to not let cookies collect your computer details. However, if you customize your Internet browser setting to block the IndianEagle server cookies, you may not be able to use certain features of our Website. If cookies are blocked on your Internet browser, your user experience may be affected. 

#### **How we protect your personal information**

By our privacy policy, we are committed to keep your personal information secure. We assure you of the strict user information security at the time of browsing our website IndianEagle.com. The website integrates advanced features to facilitate online user information security. We have an upgraded security system integrating firewall to keep the user database safe from unauthorized access. We use a high-end 'encryption' method to transmit your personal information to our database system.

#### **How to opt out or unsubscribe**

You may unsubscribe from IndianEagle.com by sending a request to [unsubscribe@indianeagle.com](mailto:unsubscribe@indianeagle.com) with the subject "Unsubscribe".

#### **Children's privacy**

Our website is not to be used by minors children whose age is 13 years or under it though we book flights for young travelers. Underage children are not among our target audience. So, we don't collect their personal details as per our privacy policy. 

#### **Access to your personal information**

If you ever want to change or update the personal information that you have shared with us, log in to your "My Eagle" account and update the profile. Or, you can email the change or update in regard to your personal information to us. We will update your profile accordingly.

#### **Your privacy in legal cases**

We have the right to share your personal details with the lawyer in case of legal or judicial proceeding over hacking of your user account, unauthorized access to your profile or misuse of your personal information.

We have the right to modify our Privacy Policy at any time. We will send an email to notify you about the modification. The modified or newly added terms of the Privacy policy will be effective once updation of the page is completed. If you continue using our Website, it shows your consent to accept the updated or modified Privacy Policy.

If you have any query about any term of the IndianEagle Privacy Policy, please do get in touch with us at [privacy@indianeagle.com.](mailto:privacy@indianeagle.com)
